<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Focal Point</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>

    <string-array name="months_array">
        <item>January</item>
        <item>February</item>
        <item>March</item>
        <item>April</item>
        <item>May</item>
        <item>June</item>
        <item>July</item>
        <item>August</item>
        <item>September</item>
        <item>October</item>
        <item>November</item>
        <item>December</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="years_array">
        <item>2016</item>
        <item>2017</item>
        <item>2018</item>
    </string-array>

        <string name="app_description_string">Focal Point is a student project written in Android Studios.
            Equipt with a google log in and the mysqlite database, the writing of this app was a great learning
        experience. The app visuals were made with Inkscape, and the generic widgets have been modified to improve
        the apps aesthetics. </string>

    <string name="known_bugs_description_string">Although pretty awesome, Focal Point is still in it\'s early stages, and has a few bugs.
      \n Here are few that I\'m aware of: \n-List runs out of memory and crashes if scrolled too fast
        (it was implemented with a View holder for  the CheckBox)
     \n -App crashes if moved off screen and some other phone functionality is used, while loading a page.
     \n -App doesn\'t account for the pushing Start Focusing button while timer is at 0.
     \n -The graph page isn\'t completely finished. Spinner Listeners aren\'t implemented.</string>
     \n -This app DOES NOT work with all apps. I\'d need to come up with a better search algorithm to improve the number of apps it works with.
    There is a mixture of package names, and app names and there is no set standard for the assignment of those names.

    <string name="ack_description_string">Thanks to Jared Rummler for his work with the Android Shell. My application would\'ve been
        impossible without that. The new security that android implemented make some built in functions not work the way they\'re expected. I also
        made use of StackOverflow, Youtube,Vogella, Google(API site), TutorialPoint, and developer.android. I\'m really grateful for all of these resources.
    </string>

</resources>
